[English subtitles are available.]
In this episode,
we only have Sis to accompany us.
Peng Yuchang
is doing his acting work in some deep forest.
Zhang Yixing
is engaged in a very important performance
in Beijing.
Sis is the only reliable one.
The two boys are
unreliable.
Being too ambitious for career is not that good.
Especially when the career is not that
magnificent.
Do I look
just like a local?
If it weren't for your
upright hairstyle,
I would think you were local.
Hi.
How are you?
Easy, she's not pregnant with her second child.
Hello.
You were laborious.
Laborious... You wanna do him a favor?
This place is really good.
Oh, I can't do it.
Too petite.
You are way too petite
to carry such heavy luggage.
Thank you, Mr. Shen.
Let me fan for you.
The house looks nice.
When I'm old,
I hope to live in such a house.
Hello.
Why do I see that
there are two colors in the sea?
Yeah, because of the ocean current.
It makes the sea color different in the distance.
It's deeper blue.
Our lemons are growing again.
Really.
They proved themselves.
I thought they would grow slowly.
They grew quite fast.
I thought they'd be intertwined.
But they didn't.
Look how beautiful Sis is on my camera.
Look, Sis.
Do you like it?
I'll send the pictures to our WeChat group.
Okay.
I'm telling you,
in this episode,
we only have Sis to accompany us.
Sis is the only reliable one.
Exactly.
The two boys are
unreliable.
Being too ambitious for career is not that good.
Especially when the career is not that
magnificent.
Not that bad actually.
So the current situation is that
the three of us
eat less.
Less mouths to eat.
Less mouths.
But less hands, too.
The two boys,
if quickly,
will probably come back tonight.
Only if quickly.
But if slowly, only god knows when
they'll be back.
If they couldn't come back tonight...
How many seashells do we have?
Come come count count,
two four six seven eight.
Count inside the house.
It's hot outside.
Sit over there. It's cool.
Count in the kitchen. It's cool.
They are beautiful.
It's so hot! You can touch it.
It's really hot.
Beautiful!
Mr. Huang, it's windy here.
So comfortable.
Five.
Here.
Ten.
Fifteen.
Twenty-five.
So many.
Thirty.
We have thirty?
Thirty-six.
We have 36 seashells.
Then we don't have to work.
Mr. Huang,
do you think they'll approve of this one?
Mr. He,
is this one
exactly the same as their seashells?
Yes, exactly.
Then I'm going to put it into the jar.
Thirty-six.
We have 36 seashells.
Is there anything
we can unlock now?
Director.
It's hot outside.
So I'll talk to you right here.
How do you do?
With this distance,
it's like greeting with each other.
Yeah.
What?
The seashells are...
You have already unlocked the cars
with the first 20 seashells, right?
Right.
The next thing to unlock is the tree house.
Can we unlock it now?
No, you need another four seashells.
But you said every 20 seashells unlock a tool.
Yes. You unlock the cars when you have 20.
Then you unlock the tree house when you have 40.
Then you unlock the next tool when you have 80.
So the first 20
are not included, right?
No, you are wrong.
If we want to unlock the tree house,
they'll give us another 40 seashells, right?
Failed to fool him.
I failed.
Fine, he's smart.
I got it.
We need another 4 seashells
to unlock the tree house.
So how can we get more seashells?
Now.
Please refer to Old fisherman's Handbook.
Okay.
Counting fish.
This works.
It will work.
Two four six seven eight.
It's just like counting ducks. Everyone can do it.
Come come count count,
two four six seven eight.
Nice.
Okay then.
We'll do that later.
Are there any guests coming?
If there are, can we ask them to do it?
Is that okay?
Mr. He,
we need someone with sharp eyes...
Yes.
...a quick mind
and a good memory.
While counting
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9,10...
15,
the counter forgets the number.
That's unqualified, you know.
Great.
Master!
Master! Mr. Huang!
Sis!
Why am I so miserable?
Uncle Shen!
Why didn't you ask for a hand?
Jiong!
Babe!
Mr. Huang!
Welcome.
Come here.
Come in, Mary.
Mr. Huang.
You were really enjoying it,
when someone fanned for you
even while walking.
Then we found that
you were carrying all the luggage.
That's the quid pro quo.
This is Zhang Zifeng.
Hello.
Hi, Sis.
Watching her films while growing up.
We watch her films while she grows up.
I thought you mean you watched her films
to grow up.
Uncle Shen's coming!
Ma Li's coming!
Welcome.
Put luggage in the room.
I'll put Ma Li's luggage
in the girls' room.
It's over there. Let me help you.
I can do it.
No, I'll do it for you.
I love this place.
If I can live here when I'm old...
You bet.
Are we gonna sleep here tonight?
Yeah, is that okay for you to share this room
with Sis?
Absolutely!
Sleep facing the window.
Look, the seaside is just over there.
My dreaming house.
We are really living our life here.
The girls live in this room?
It's like living in a movie.
I'll bring you slippers.
Okay.
Find slippers for Ma Li.
Mr. He,
are you making a special mark for her?
Yes.
These are especially for me.
Yeah, especially for you.
Can I take them with me
when you finish it, Master?
Of course you can.
Thank you, Master.
You can take off your socks.
Okay.
Isn't it more comfortable?
Ma Li.
Are they cute?
So cute.
Look, my special slippers.
The ML mark is especially for me.
Initials of Ma Li.
My Master made it for me.
Do you want it?
Not really.
Mr. Shen, why don't you change larger ones?
These are too small for you.
Not small. Are they small?
Your heels are coming out.
But I don't think you can find a larger size.
We do have slippers in Size 43.
Do you?
Then I want to change.
Let me help you.
Whatever Ma Li has,
Shen Teng must have it, too.
Am I right?
I was not jealous.
Absolutely not.
The special slippers are worth treasuring.
Here, these are more comfortable.
Jiong, you are so thoughtful.
Are they small?
It'd be better if there are some larger ones.
Why are your feet so big?
Bigfoot Shen.
You know what?
Slippers should be one or two sizes
larger than your normal.
But Mr. Bigfoot,
these slippers on your feet
are a little small.
I'm only wearing like this to pretend I'm a local.
Size 43 is the largest we have.
It's okay. Don't worry.
I can stand it.
Wait.
Just leave it to me.
I can do it, Jiong.
-How can I...
-What are you doing?
How can I leave it to you?
The camera's here.
It's a blind angle.
Fine. Look.
When you help me,
you should face that camera.
I was wondering
why there's no camera inside the cabinet.
Really?
Because it's not even a work.
Missed the camera.
Here, Uncle Shen.
I'll pour them out for you.
I can't pick them up.
Jiong, stand up.
There's a camera.
Have a rest.
You can sit over here
and work,
and then you casually
and handsomely turn around. Right.
His eyes were misty.
Disgusting.
Here come the fish-counters.
It suddenly came to me.
Shen Teng,
come and sit.
How's your eyesight?
Just so so.
Okay.
What about memory?
Even worse.
Eyesight is better.
Okay.
I was looking for someone
who has a bad eyesight and memory.
That's you!
Mary.
How's your eyesight?
Pretty good.
Okay.
How about your memory?
Excellent.
Good.
You can just
make up a team.
What team?
It's called "we count each other".
Shen Ma Team.
You can call it like this.
Why?
Because you are counting fish later.
Counting fish.
Then I'll choose Sis to team with me.
Just sit and have a rest.
Mr. He doesn't need a seat.
Look, a bug!
Wait, is it a bug?
No, it looks like a piece of cauliflower.
It seems that your eyesight is not so good, Sis.
Is that ice coffee?
Awesome!
The two strong labors are not here today...
Right, did you notice that two people missing?
Yes.
Peng and
Yixing are not here.
We need two labors,
and you two showed up.
What's this music for? A musical play?
Yes.
Show us a solo dance, bro!
The directors are summoning us.
Shall we go now?
It's okay. You can take the tea.
I'm a black swan.
The black swan is coming.
What does it mean?
It means an activity.
Whenever there are activities,
the directors will play this music.
Xixi and the director are wearing suits!
Isn't that our Party A, Wang?
Yes, it is.
Why are you wearing a suit, Wang?
Don't miss it!
Have a look at our goods.
Manager Wang.
Manager Wang, right?
What's this?
What does it mean?
In order to help you guys
upgrade from novice fishermen to old fishermen,
we The Shark Group in the north bay
launched a new special offer,
called "Shark Loan".
I was also promoted gloriously
from the captain of "the Shark" to...
Credit Manager.
Yes.
Have a look at our new business.
What's this?
Help novice fishermen move forward warm.
Interest free loan for novice fishermen.
Help you realize fishing freedom in three days,
seafood freedom in seven days.
It's kind of attractive.
This is our previous
success case.
Let me see it.
Why does he look so indecent?
But you have to admit that
the other day he caught
a small shark (farmed sharks for market),
and showed it to everyone.
Let me show you that
in Shayutang Village,
we caught
a small shark (farmed sharks for market).
This is its mouth.
It's still alive and shaking.
That's true.
He really caught it,
a small shark (farmed sharks for market).
You didn't have any tools,
so last time when you went fishing at the sea
you borrowed the net from brother Bo, right?
Right.
Actually there are all sorts of net.
You never catch fish without a proper net.
Let me introduce the nets for you.
There are two kinds of gill net.
They are all for fishing at the sea.
What brother Bo used last time was a gill net.
It was...
We caught a flying fish last time.
This is for inshore fishing.
Throw it into the sea and the crabs will catch it.
This is for inshore pulling.
You walk into the sea and throw it,
without taking a boat.
Fish cages, you've tried before.
From brother Bo.
Right.
This one is the best.
This is what Xixi used the other day
to catch a small shark (farmed sharks for market).
Light trapping.
For night fishing.
Right.
So these are important tools for you
to convert from poor to rich.
The reason why we caught few seafood last time
is that we didn't have these tools.
Exactly. Last time when you went fishing
with brother Bo,
your harvests were poor, right?
You are backbiting brother Bo.
Does he know it?
Yes.
How come he knows it?
So what are you doing?
Are you selling them?
No, we are offering loans.
How can we get a loan?
You don't have money, right?
You don't have money.
We assessed your house.
We can offer you a loan
during your startup.
Here's what I think,
Mr. Huang,
we need the kitchen.
We don't necessarily need the kitchen.
No.
Can we eat outside?
I will not cook.
Let's get RMB 2000 out of it
and get an eel cage.
We can dine with the rest, which is RMB 1200,
right?
This is one way to do it.
We can just get RMB 2000 worth of fish.
No.
We can get rid of the kitchen
and exchange it for money.
The money will be enough for a few days.
The problem is this Shark Loan
won't give you actual money.
It takes your property,
but only gives you tools in return.
Then just take my house
as collateral.
Which one is yours?
Which one of these is yours?
The old man's house.
That's mine.
That's yours?
It depends on our ages.
I'm the oldest here.
Mr. He and I have the old man's house.
Yes. You'll get the
luxury ocean view house
with the teens.
You will live with the teens.
There's an amazing ocean view house up there.
There it is.
Look at that,
the one on the top floor,
That's mine.
What about the balcony?
Sure.
We don't need the balcony.
Let's mortgage the balcony.
Okay.
Let's do it.
We'll mortgage the balcony.
Wait, how can I get out of my room then?
Why don't you mortgage my room
and the balcony?
Oh.
He has a point.
I can't get out of my room without the balcony.
Indeed he can't.
True.
How should he get in?
Right.
Hold on.
Uncle Shen can live in the living room.
That'll do.
That is the guest's room at the first place.
Honestly, I think we can mortgage both of them.
Alright, we'll mortgage them both.
It's RMB 3000 for them both.
What should we buy with RMB 3000?
How much are these together
for six items?
RMB 2200,
RMB1400,
They total up to RMB 3000.
Give me a discount.
We have to bargain.
RMB 2500 for all of these.
That's not possible.
Please.
I can't.
Let us have RMB 500 of spare money
in case of emergencies,
is that fine?
You can get another loan.
We have nothing left
for another loan.
We have to eat and to live.
Can you take just RMB 2500?
We don't have cash.
I can't give you RMB 500 in cash.
I mean,
just in case,
can you put RMB 500
on our account?
We're friends,
right?
We...
Mr. He said RMB 2500.
Awesome.
RMB 2600.
RMB 2500 please.
Here's what I think.
RMB 2500 sounds fair.
Just now
Mr. Shen saw you in stockings.
He's wearing stockings.
Yes.
The sandals are too large.
He's wearing stockings
with huge sandals.
I can't bear watching it.
I feel so bad.
I'm not wearing stockings.
You are.
Did you forget about it?
I feel so bad.
I can't take it.
He's upset.
Think of the RMB 100
as compensation for damage to mental health.
It makes sense.
Okay?
RMB 2500. Fine.
Alright then.
If you take a close look,
they're made of cotton.
They're made of cotton,
but he has washed them too many times
that they look like stockings.
Well, they're too thin now.
True.
Sign the contract here.
Sis, go ahead.
Go for it.
If I sign it, we can't take it back.
But if you do it,
you can act like you don't know
You don't know what happened
because you are still young.
Right.
Write the party B
as Family H.
Family H
borrowed in total
of RMB 3000
for the set.
RMB 3000.
And I'll add the note
that it's been discounted to RMB 2500.
Fingerprint here.
Okay.
Normally,
business owners will offer wet tissues
for clients to wipe their fingers
clean afterwards.
Right.
Don't say that
you don't have wet tissues.
If not, we'll take another discount.
No way.
You can use my stockings.
Hurry, let's go.
You're so funny.
It's our first doing this.
Really?
We've never had such business before.
We can go count fishes later.
Here's the thing.
There's a job called fish counting.
A fish counter
is the middle man between a buyer and a seller.
Are you a person?
Do you belong to the human kind?
I think so.
I'm a person.
You belong to the human kind.
You're a person.
Okay. You two are fish counters.
So gross.
They are renting the place.
What?
Rent directly from the owner, and move in soon.
That's bad.
Yeah.
Mr. He,
look.
We are banned to go in.
How can you
do this to us?
They've even sealed it.
That's bad.
That's terrible.
Xixi, what are you doing?
Delivering those
all over the place.
Are those for us?
Yes.
Alright.
What is that?
Xixi, what is that?
This is a gift
for our clients.
Roast piglet.
Awesome!
What?
I've never seen anyone
taking raw pigs as gifts.
Same here.
Really.
Mr. Huang, don't.
No!
Here's also a schedule table.
Here's what we can do
during this time.
Mr. He,
take a look.
Look.
I'll pass on the piglet.
Are you eating it
after I roast it?
Yes.
Funny.
Mr. Huang,
if you get it done, we'll get ten shells.
How many?
Roast piglet.
A famous Hainan fish.
The piglet of the east.
The fifth famous dish hidden in Hainan.
It's roasted traditionally for 90 minutes.
Okay.
I'll go marinate it now.
Let me put the piglet here.
It's easier with trousers on.
Right?
There's a new friend in the living room.
Have a look.
I mean the kitchen.
A new friend?
Newer than us?
Here it is.
I thought it's a person.
Look again.
Here?
No.
Wow it's so pale.
Look, Ma Li is not scared.
She's not.
She's brave.
Mr. He,
let's go count the fishes.
Okay.
I'll take care of it.
I'll
marinate it here.
I'll go find you guys after I'm done.
Alright, let's go.
Go.
Come on.
I have this feeling that
I've blend in the local culture well,
especially with these trousers and the T-shirt.
Yes.
Hi.
This place looks chill.
Hello.
A hammock.
That's awesome.
Nice.
Such a big fishpond.
Hello.
Hi.
Hi there.
Hi, I'm He Jiong.
What should I call you?
Mr. Dong.
And you?
Mr. Chen.
Mr. Chen, right?
Okay. Mr. Dong and Mr. Chen.
He asked if I have good eyesight.
Are we counting these?
Wow.
This is not going to be easy.
Are we counting these?
We are counting these, right?
Oh my goodness.
Count these.
There are a lot.
What are those?
I can't count these.
What are these?
Pearl,
pearl fish.
They're small.
Do you eat them this small?
They're raising them.
These are babies,
baby fishes.
How do you count them?
Do you take them out and then count?
Right.
Take them out to count.
How are we going to do that?
I see.
You take one basket of them out.
Yes.
Put them in this fishpond.
Right?
Put them in this basket.
Right.
I got it.
One, two, three, four, five
seven, eight. There're eight of them.
Nine.
Eight,
Okay.
Okay. Let's begin.
Guys. Let's do it.
Here.
Come on.
No. Stop playing.
This one is huge.
12, 16.
12 plus 6 is 18.
19, 20, 21, 22,
23, 24, 25,
26, 27.
I think we should work like this.
I'll take them out
and you count them.
There're too many. I can't count them right.
Let's take it slow.
Don't move.
25, 35, 45, 55,
56, 57, 58.
How many are there?
58, right?
10 here.
How many were there?
So 70 in total.
Let's see who gets to 500 first.
Okay.
14 plus 8.
22 plus 7.
The other team is too loud.
Alright.
89 plus 6.
How many is that?
45, 46, 47,
48, 49, 50.
9 plus 4.
There're too many.
I can't count.
64, 65.
5 more.
How many?
3 more here.
78 plus 6.
85 plus 7.
66 is a good number.
76 plus 8.
A plural adds a plural and we get a single number?
What is that?
82 plus 9.
You count it.
Can you?
Okay.
You should do it.
I'm bad at counting.
One.
4, 6, 8, 10, 12.
I will do it.
It's fine.
Let me.
It's okay.
Let me do it.
You're repeating yourself.
My eyes are not working well.
Wait.
Let me do it.
You said you'll do it
and he took another basket.
I'll do it.
Go ahead.
I'll take them out.
78 plus 4.
82, 83.
You can do it.
Take some.
Teng,
I thought you are not afraid of fish.
How many are there?
Oh, no.
I have 3.
You had five ones there.
Plus eight more.
Three more should get it right.
How many did you have before those five?
Let's put a stick here once we get to 100.
Jiong!
We forgot the number
after you interrupted.
How many were there?
I don't know.
We lost count.
Little piglet.
Cute little piglet.
Done.
I'll go for a walk.
I'll check on them.
I have to bow down.
29 plus 4.
29 plus 4 equals to 33, right?
34, 35, 36, 37,
Do you have facial tissues?
I need to clean my eyes.
I'll get some for you.
Here.
38 plus 10, 48.
Okay.
My lower back hurts.
Master, wipe your sweats.
Jiong!
You're really sweating this time.
It's too hot.
My fingers are tired.
My finger hurts.
It feels like
a sauna room in here.
What's the number again?
I lost it.
How are you doing?
Mr. Huang.
This is hard, right?
This grouper fish
is so small.
These are baby fishes.
They're small.
Mr. Huang, how's your lower back?
Not so good.
My body hurts a lot.
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine
87 plus 4.
That's wrong.
One, that's one.
It's time.
Let's go.
I'll count some for you.
Take some, we'll take some more too.
Here.
Victory is in sight, guys.
Okay.
Nine.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
Eighty-five.
Nineteen, twenty-nine.
Forty-three!
Sixty-eight, sixty-nine.
Seventy-one.
Thirty-two, thirty-three, thirty-four, thirty-five,
thirty-six, thirty-seven.
33 plus 6 is 39.
39 plus 8!
Forty-seven!
47 plus 10!
Fifty-seven!
Forty-six. It comes to a bottleneck now.
61 plus 5!
Sixty-six!
Fifty!
Twenty-three.
61 plus 5!
Sixty-six!
One, two, three, four, five, six.
Twenty-three.
Plus 4!
What?
What plus 4?
57 plus 4.
Thirty-six.
Forty-six!
Forty-seven!
Fifty!
Eighty-two, eighty-three, eighty-four, eighty-five,
eighty-six, eighty-seven!
One hundred!
89 plus 6!
It's such a mess.
Stop your competition, okay?
Okay!
Five hundred.
Okay.
That's enough.
So we counted...
We counted one thousand and five hundred.
Did you count one thousand and five hundred?
I counted eight hundred and fifty.
Right.
You are amazing.
You counted eight hundred alone.
You counted more than eight hundred?
Right.
With a hundred and fifty more,
I'll achieve the number of one thousand
soon.
These aren't counted yet, right?
Okay, give them to me.
Now we start to
pursue the sense of achievement.
We must finish counting all of them, right?
Right.
Sixty.
Sixty-two.
Sixty-four.
Sixty-seven.
Eighty, eighty-one, eighty-two, eighty-three,
eighty-four, eighty-five, eighty-six!
Eighty-six, eighty-eight.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight, nine,
ten, eleven, twelve.
Eighty-three.
Fourteen, fifteen.
Sixteen, seventeen.
Eighteen.
Nineteen.
Eighty-six. 86 plus 12.
Ninety-eight.
Twenty-three, twenty-four.
56 plus 12 is 68.
Seventy-one, seventy-two.
Sixty-nine.
Seventy-two,
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
44 plus 5 is 49.
Seventy-four, seventy-nine.
Eighty, eighty-one, eighty-two,
eighty-three, eighty-four!
51 plus 8 is 59.
Sixty-two.
Sixty-seven.
Sixty-eight, sixty-nine.
Only one basket left.
We're almost finished!
Eleven, twelve, thirteen.
Here.
Here you are.
Exactly nine.
Add one hundred to the number.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
Eighty.
I've got one thousand here.
Thirty.
Ninety.
Thirty-three.
Four hundred and twenty-three, right?
Right.
Good.
There are two thousand here. Don't move the fries.
Done. Four thousand, nine hundred and twenty-three.
Give me a tissue.
Mary, give me a tissue.
Tissue.
I totally didn't expect that
I had to take a shower at only 3 p.m.
It's terrible.
Didn't they say there would be no work?
How long does it take to raise a fish?
About ten to twelve months.
How much is it?
About thirty-five to forty yuan per jin.
[*Equals to 70 - 80 RMB/kg]
So...
A mature fish weighs about two jin.
[*Equals to 1 kg]
About one jin and a half.
[*Equals to 0.75 kg]
One jin and a half.
So a mature fish is worth sixty yuan or so.
Sixty to seventy yuan.
What's the profit of one fish?
More than half of the earning.
OK, guys, let's go.
Done.
They will recheck it.
I'll do the test count.
Do it.
Do the test count.
Okay.
How about recheck the basket with 500 fries?
Four hundred and twenty-three, right?
Yeah, four hundred and twenty-three.
I'll test this one.
Okay.
Thank you.
Not at all.
Let me learn the way you count.
How can you count if you do so?
In this way, he doesn't need to bend over.
Right.
I did the same,
to avoid bending.
Count five by five.
It's a smart way.
We all did this way.
Only you didn't.
Four hundred and twenty-three.
Exactly the number.
Pass!
Thank you!
Guys, let's go!
Listen.
There are
five thousand fish here.
Five thousand, you know.
The profit of one fish is thirty yuan.
The five thousand fish
will make a profit of 150 thousand yuan in a year.
That's good, right?
May you earn a lot.
May you make a fortune.
I'm so proud
when the test count number
was exactly the same with what we counted.
Cheers, guys!
The fish are for you.
Thank you!
I raised them myself.
You're welcome.
Thank you, boss.
They're so big!
There are two fish!
Let's cook them tonight.
Thank you, boss.
I'm so proud!
Thank you!
Bye!
Drive safe!
Okay. Bye!
Let's roast pork tonight.
And a braised...
Steamed fish, for the better.
We should steam the groupers.
Steamed groupers are delicious.
They taste better when steamed.
With shredded scallion.
Should we leave a fish for the two young men?
There's no need.
They may not arrive on time.
It's okay.
Ignore them.
We lost our house.
We don't need to think about them.
Let's wash hands.
I'll go wash my hands.
The two little fish are indeed wild groupers.
I'll marinate them.
[The ad is aired at this period of time]
Let's move the grill
here.
Okay. Let's go.
Let's place it in the center. The C position.
You place it in the center?
Later you ignite it, okay?
Okay. I'll ignite the coal.
I'm a native of Qiqihar.
Qiqihar is home of BBQ, right?
Leave the coal ignition to me.
Do we have LPG?
Yes.
Head of coal from Qiqihar
is going to give you a lesson.
Those who haven't eaten BBQ for 20 years
cannot even
think of this idea.
But we all do the same.
We all do so.
No wonder nobody sounds amazed.
And I wanted to say,
since you asked about LPG,
I wanted to say
you were going to use LPG to ignite the coal.
But I didn't expect
you'd have a look that, like,
you were the only one knowing this on earth.
Wait and see.
Uncle Shen, did you ignite coal in Mahua shows?
No.
The title of king of, head of coal from Qiqihar...
Doesn't help.
No wonder today
you kept giving me the feeling
that the whole world was yours.
In the world, except your brother...
Except Uncle Shen.
Sis,
do you know how funny it is?
When I worked with Shen Teng when we were young,
I called him Uncle Shen.
He called me Bro Jiong.
Our oral relationship
is always confusing.
Uncle and...
Because he looked old at a young age.
I looked old when I was young.
He looked mature then?
Right.
He was handsome.
But he wasn't...
He just looked older than me.
Actually, before
I work long
with Mr. Huang,
I was working with Shen Teng first.
Right.
We worked together.
We started in 2003
to act in plays.
In 2003.
Almost twenty years ago.
So what?
It's been almost 20 years.
How about we celebrate it tonight?
For the twenty years.
Let's do it.
I'll take the pig out.
It's in here?
It smells so good!
The sauce.
I'm smelling it.
I'll fasten its head.
A little further down, I think.
Yes.
Bun tightening.
Right. Bun tightening.
I tied it up pretty well.
Yes.
I'll simply oil and roast it.
For ninety minutes.
It needs five thousand turns.
Then there must be someone always turning it over.
Right.
We can take turns to do it.
I'll definitely shoot a video
and send it to the two young men.
Yixing will be like,
"Wow, master, this,"
"this is amazing!"
Don't move
Professional profile.
Look at his face.
It looks like somebody owes money to him.
Nothing.
Love you.
I take charge of the fire so well.
When will you finish?
Coming.
Soon.
We're coming!
Come.
Let's go.
Which side do I go to?
It doesn't matter on which side we sit.
This side.
Okay.
Clockwise.
Which floor? The second or first?
Here. Right.
Turn it!
Right.
No.
You need to roast it a while before turning it.
That's not how we roast it.
Right. Roast it a while.
It'll take some time.
You take the charge.
Now?
Take it, then.
Here.
Here. Uncle Shen, please have a seat.
I put the spade here.
To prevent the pig from being robbed of?
To prevent the pig from being robbed of.
Is your face burned, bro?
Not mine, but its face.
Its face.
You need to turn it, right?
Won't you turn it?
No.
Better turn it. Don't get it charred.
Don't worry.
It needs turning over constantly
based on the guide.
Yeah, I have a guide.
You gotta turn it.
You have a guide?
Right.
Then I don't insist.
I'll just follow the guide.
Yeah, you gotta turn it.
But the heat isn't high enough.
I gotta turn it slightly.
Directors asked you to roast it quickly.
You may get it charred easily.
You must turn it over constantly.
See?
Hurry!
Directors,
you do it!
But I think in this way...
You gotta turn it.
You're elegant.
If the surface gets dry, we gotta oil it.
Before...
You add the oil too early.
Fine. You do it.
It's all your work. I'll cook the rice.
If you're tired,
just call us.
I'm afraid you can't do it.
Someone is watching the time, right?
After it's smoked,
oh my,
it will be stunning.
It smells good.
Still long to go.
Are you tired?
No.
Not at all.
Let me do it.
Let me move the charcoal over there.
Great.
It looks so good.
Really, it's colored. Nice.
The pig looks so nice.
-It's good?
-It's good.
So nice.
Thank you.
Come in for a while?
Okay.
Come in here.
It's cool inside.
Thank you.
Gotta close the door.
Do we have a guitar?
Yes!
And speakers?
I think so.
I'll play the guitar for you while you're working.
You can play the guitar, bro?
Li.
You only played the lute.
Why do you have to climb that high?
Be safe.
Uncle Shen,
if it's darker,
you may play in the sunset.
We roast the pig under
while you're over there.
It's...
See? Your image
will be quite different, right?
God of art.
And the toiling people.
To hardworking Jiong,
Mr. Huang,
and sis.
Thank you.
And to my best partner, Mary!
He plays well.
So nice.
Uncle Shen, you're amazing.
Uncle Shen practiced it specially for the show.
Really?
This is good.
Good.
Yixing
Yixing can play the guitar.
But not as good as him.
Yeah, not as good as him.
It sounds like string music.
Not just guitar,
but other musical instruments.
I love his playing.
He really knows how to control the plucking force.
It seems like he plucks a string,
but no sound is heard.
His playing is in tune with
the accompanying music.
Very even.
He knows how to control his force.
Right.
Like acoustics.
He is so talented.
Why is there...
Why is there accompanying music?
Sis and I should have accompanied you.
An orchestra is accompanying his playing.
This is a whole band.
I have to search for a guitar solo.
Uncle Shen, the drone is coming.
Rewind it.
Let's start again.
The drone is here.
Oh no, this is...
No guitar anymore.
Guitar is not heard anymore.
That's really dropping the ball
at the critical moment.
So annoying.
Come on.
Leave it to the post-production.
OK, let's do it again.
Right, do it again.
Do it again.
The drone is ready.
It's raining.
Mr. Huang, it's raining.
Teng,
the god is moved to tears by your playing.
So tragic.
It's so humiliating.
It's so funny.
He really wants to show off his playing.
Right.
It's really raining.
It's raining harder and harder.
Look at her.
Hold an umbrella for the little pig.
OK.
It's so romantic in a raining day.
It stops raining.
Really?
The raining
is just to accompany Mr. Shen's playing.
Teng, can you sing while playing?
I'll find a song accompanied by guitar.
You can fake just everything nowadays.
How do you sing "Love In A Life Time"?
Has it started yet?
I don't know.
Almost finished.
Not yet.
How do I start?
Just play.
Have you hit an electric switch?
Who is going to sing with me?
Jiong, sing with me.
Help me.
You scared the drone away.
You can sign up for "Songs Forever".
You sing like Hong Kong music.
Just sing a song you are good at.
Will you remember
my diary of yesterday?
Will you miss yourself
who once loved crying?
Our teachers will forget you
who once loved crying.
A little bit.
Just a little.
So beautiful.
It looks like a fairy tale.
The princess is standing at the window.
It's getting brighter.
So beautiful.
Beautiful.
The edge is on fire. So amazing.
Sis,
Mary.
The sun is coming out.
So beautiful.
Let's take a picture here.
We five people.
Hurry.
I'm coming.
Come here.
OK.
Fantastic.
Beautiful.
It's so breathtaking.
Amazing.
Beautiful.
I have some dishes to cook.
Scramble egg with sauce.
It roasted so well.
Definitely.
Done.
What are we going to do with the roast piglet,
Mr. Huang?
Take it out if it is done.
Dinner is ready.
Let's go.
Where do we place the piglet?
On the cutting board?
Yes, take the basket away.
It's done.
So good.
I suggest cutting a piece of meat
of the deeper level.
This one.
It's done.
OK.
No problem.
The pigskin smells so good.
I didn't expect the roast piglet is so good.
Roll it over.
OK.
How about this one?
Give me a pretty plate.
Two, please.
Pretty plates.
Give me two.
I'm on it.
Cut the legs first.
This one.
Well.
This is for Yixing and Peng.
This is for them.
Okay.
You know,
the shape is perfect for them.
Let me take a picture.
Mr. Huang loves you so much.
This is what he kept for you.
So naughty.
Mr. He, look at the outside.
Wow.
Turn off the light.
All flying ants are here.
Yes!
They look like catkin.
Like a scene in a disaster movie.
Turn off the light.
Lure them away.
So scary.
Look, under the house.
It's horrible.
Why did they fly here all of a sudden?
Sis, take this for me.
They all come in.
So gross.
Just leave.
Leave here.
Take these inside.
Let me take it away.
Hurry.
Hurry up.
Superb!
No ants anymore.
Just these two.
Killed by Shen Teng.
Problem solved.
Let's have dinner.
Come and take a seat.
I'll sit here.
Here.
Chopsticks, please.
I made some egg sauce for you.
Should we wait for Ma Li?
Wait for her.
Don't wait for Ma Li.
Let's start eating.
Okay.
Hurry up.
We are waiting for you.
Look, my bowl is still clean.
I just start eating.
Wow, quick respond.
Take this cushion.
You'll be more comfortable.
You are so good.
It will take me a whole day to cook this dinner.
The chicken is so good.
Looks delicious.
The sauce is so good.
Really.
So good.
Give me some shredded potatoes.
OK.
With so many dishes on the table...
Field survival
is not a problem for northeasterner.
Definitely.
Did you soak the potatoes in water before cooking?
So they're crisper.
Yeah.
Do you cook a lot?
No kidding.
The traditional "falling off the stool".
[* It refers to somebody is so shocked that he falls off the stool]
Literally.
Thanks, Master.
Thanks, Mr. Huang.
Welcome.
We're a family of five.
It feels like a family.
Very good.
Which one should I dip in?
Dip in the sauce or not?
That's OK.
You can dip in either one.
Try to dip in the chili powder.
We made the roast piglet for the first time.
Bravo.
I didn't expect it could even be cooked.
I was wondering...
And so delicious.
It will taste even better
if it were roasted a little longer.
She told me that...
Teng placed the piglet too low.
I placed too low.
It should be roasted by slow fire.
I was a little impatient.
Don't worry.
I didn't know much about the charcoal.
I wasn't sure
if the charcoal was from Qiqihar.
I didn't know if it was durable.
They were not Qiqihar charcoals.
That's the problem.
But it's so delicious.
Thanks.
Taste good?
I dare not to eat too much fat.
You can't stand a whole piece of meat.
Right.
Many people are like you.
They can only eat minced meat.
When I eat an eggplant,
sometimes I mistake it
for fat,
I feel so gross.
So you don't like something so soft.
Yeah, I can't stand something tasting like fat.
You really can't eat a piece of fat meat.
This is so good.
I'll have a piece of fattest meat.
The fat meat.
This baby.
The fat meat tastes so good.
It tastes so good.
Fat meat tastes much better.
Why are you so quiet?
You keep eating coriander.
This scene...
He likes coriander so much.
Good for you.
Do you know you
smell like coriander now?
Smell good?
No. I don't eat coriander.
Jiong!
Have a taste.
You don't eat coriander.
No.
Some people just can't stand the smell.
Jiong, do you want to
have a try?
I believe coriander tastes so good.
Raw coriander? I can't do it.
Jiong.
Why don't we do it this way?
I'll have acoriander
if you have a piece of fat meat.
We both make a breakthrough here.
I think it's a good idea.
Dumbfounded?
No, we both...
How stupid you are.
Well, fat meat is really...
But you're OK watching us eating?
Totally fine.
That's OK.
I'll have a coriander, OK?
As a gift for the "Moon Man".
Is that OK?
Speaking of the "Moon Man",
you need to eat some fatty meat.
I'll have a piece of meat.
No, you don't have to.
You have made enough sacrifices for the movie.
I do this for you and Ma Li.
I worked on this movie for almost 5 months.
And this is...
I'm about to cry.
Take this small one.
A big one is OK.
Okay, come on.
Try this one.
OK.
Well, this is...
Dip in the sauce.
Definitely.
Some more, please.
Jiong, I'm so touched.
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight, nine.
Nine pieces,
okay?
Here's the thing.
I'm very happy.
As they are both my childhood friend,
they now become successful
in films and stage plays
and also in variety shows.
I'm deeply touched,
and I think it's great.
And...right.
I, well...
Where's the fatty meat?
I'm gonna bring that piglet over.
Mr. Shen wants to eat the fatty meat.
No.
Let's wait till two young people come.
They have theirs.
He rolled his eyes.
You're not gonna get away with this.
Is this all?
Yes, I made them all.
It must taste good now
when grilling removes grease.
I should put more charcoals for the two young men.
No, you just have the fatty meat first.
You don't get in.
Pure fatty meat here.
It doesn't even have the crispy skin.
Beating around the bush is not gonna help.
We're talking about you now.
You pick this one.
Have this.
Find a small one, Mr. Shen.
You can eat with coriander.
I'll eat with you.
Let's do it for Moon Man, okay?
Let's be happy.
Seriously,
I got physiological response.
Physiological response already?
You pick one.
This's so lean.
If you eat this, I'll just...
Then why do you need coriander, right?
Right.
You pick one fairly.
Perhaps this one.
This one is leaner.
Look at this one.
This works.
Half-half.
This's so the one!
It tastes great with chili powder.
Wrap the leanest one with chili power.
Come on!
Just a second.
I need more of this.
Will you throw up?
No.
Neither of us will.
Let's hold it back, right?
Okay.
For Moon Man, okay?
Moon Man.
The film will be quite popular.
Thanks, Mr. He.
Shen Teng, Ma Li
He can't swallow it.
It's delicious?
Force it down.
Swallow it
in a whole.
Want tissues?
I'm swallowing saliva.
Stop chewing. Stop.
Yeah, don't do that.
Just swallow it.
He cannot.
Imagine it's a pill.
You can spit it out.
Master, you win.
It won't affect the result.
It's nothing to do with the result.
At least you tried, right?
Mr. He, can't believe after all these years
I still owe you one.
You're not.
You did great.
Some were suffering, some were not.
He faced a bigger challenge than me.
Mr. Huang,
because that one I ate has the sauce you made,
and I swallow it in a whole.
Actually with the egg sauce, the rice
and the noodles are good.
Everything is fine.
Cook some...
Cook some noodles
You want it?
Want it or not?
Yes.
I'll cook some noodles.
Wait a moment.
You should wait.
Now you're...He's full.
No, I'm not.
You have to eat it now?
Yes, he is,
or he won't feel like eating it later.
Shen Teng wants some noodles.
Let me server him some.
Mr. Huang is amazing.
He's bustling out around the kitchen.
I think he's talented.
Mr. Huang is really a role model.
He's the typical
Jack of all trades.
He's cooking noodles for you, but you...
What did you just say? You cruel boy.
Cameras are everywhere.
I can't wait until Mr. Huang come back.
I was gonna tell Mr. Huang.
That's...
about respect of others.
Mr. He has been very influential to me,
in terms of respect of others.
I mean it.
Well, this's all because of the coriander.
I have to respond.
I really do.
We won't...
We're not that kind of person
who likes to butter up,
but he did teach us
a lot of things.
His dedication in theatre rehearsal,
and that kind of...
meticulous care to others.
You flattered me.
During the rehearsal,
if you told him that you had a headache,
or your arms, legs or butt hurt,
maybe you were just simply saying at that time,
the other day Mr. He bring medicines
for you.
That's what he is.
We learnt a lot from him
about how to show respect.
Otherwise, we probably wouldn't get
what we have now.
Back then Xie Na...
Xie Na wants me to be there with her.
At that time,
it had a perfect atmosphere to create,
and that play went popular,
and then we created
the brand of Mahua FunAge.
Right.
And then, later she...
Ma Li was performing a play
in little theater.
I watched one of her plays three times,
and I worked my ways out to find her.
So, you know, I'm her fans.
I keep saying that.
Remember?
I remember.
It's true.
I met master
when you need to
have a skit in Hunan TV Station.
Coincidently...
he said
he knew a female actress
who performed stage plays,
named Ma Li.
Did that work? Nobody knew her.
He said, I trusted her.
I just graduated,
and had never been in a live show.
Never ever.
That day I felt like
that was the first live show in my life.
Super Happy Insoles
Right.
I was feeling inferior back then,
and I didn't dare to meet
those celebrities
or face a big scene.
I kept going backwards,
but master
kept moving ahead with me.
It is the same when we met Mr. Huang, right?
Master volunteered to introduce me.
This's Ma Li,
or she's a good actress.
Right.
She's skillful at acting.
He introduced me to everyone,
and always kept me sitting next to him.
That's necessary.
If I sat far away from him,
he'd be afraid I would feel insecure.
Like Mr. Shen,
I'm not good at buttering up
or flattering others,
but for those who helped us,
I'll keep it all in mind for a lifetime.
Since then, I called Mr. He master.
He brought me to the TV industry.
She's funny.
She's just...I worked with her
in just several shows.
Five years.
Right.
But the problem is that
she has insisted calling me master.
Yes, I don't care if you like it or not.
I never called anyone Master before.
Let me tell you.
I envied you at that time.
Right?
Yeah.
In the Mahua FunAge,
I set foot in the TV industry
earlier than anyone else.
Remember Goodbye Mr. Loser?
Yeah, we were like idiots.
Nobody knew us at that time.
We wouldn't be invited in any shows.
I asked
the master
if we can publicize it a bit?
Without the slightest hesitation,
you told me to wait,
and went out to make a call.
I texted you that
master told us to wait.
A while later, you came back
and told me that we could come.
I was crying out of joy.
I can vividly remember it.
I very easily
fell for their movies.
At the time of Goodbye Mr. Loser,
at that time,
I attended their press conference.
At that time,
I posted on Weino to promote my friend's movie.
He had posted for several days!
Each for a day,
and I came with different promotion ideas each day.
Well, a volunteered marketing specialist.
Nobody cared about us.
We begged for help,
but no one took us seriously.
In Mr. He's lifetime,
Mr. He thinks more of others than of himself.
No, it's not like that.
I'm not exaggerating.
If they know you,
they can understand.
Right.
A person always consider for himself,
but there're some people
worth your efforts of caring.
I think this's a wonderful thing.
Thank you, Master.
Come on.
Let's give the best wishes.
Thank you, master.
Yeah, let's have a toast.
Care for each other and have a wonderful life.
Wish each other a wonderful life.
[The ad is aired at this period of time]
Buddy, have some noodles.
I'll fetch that plate over.
[The ad is aired at this period of time]
Alright, let's get back.
I'm serving you the noodles.
Be back right away.
Here.
Thank you for your hard work.
This...
I want this too.
Grab a little bowl
Take it.
I want a bite.
I really want some.
She said she didn't want it five minutes ago.
It smells good.
I'm hungry.
It smells great, really.
I fried scallion to make the oil.
No wonder.
Would you like to go to the sea
tomorrow, Mr. Huang?
Yes.
Right, check the list.
We can go to the sea from 7 to 9 A.M.
After that,
we can pick up seafood on the beach at 9 A.M.
Pick one of them, or we split.
One goes to the sea, the other picks up seafood.
I am okay.
I wake up early.
You wake up early.
Right.
You can go to the sea.
Yes, I can.
Dude, I wake you up at that time.
Don't mess up with me.
His promise can't last two seconds.
Yeah, and he told me to go to the sea.
I also want to go to the sea tomorrow morning.
Whatever you like.
Look, you have to sleep early.
You wake up at eight A.M.
Then you can go to the sea.
Then I have to sleep at half past seven.
I wash my face and it's eight A.M.
Why?
Do you sleep badly? You...
Master, let me put it in this way.
We shared an apartment
when we prepared for the Spring Festival
Gala show,
The other day I saw several people
outside the door.
They took turns to wake him up,
but it didn't work.
He couldn't hear them.
I'm not sure about this time,
but anyways, he was young at that time.
Now,
it's worse due to hearing loss.
You sleep sound when you don't have pressures.
Do you wake up...
Is it really hard for you to wake up early?
My mom told me when I was in my 20s,
I still kicked her
when she woke me up.
Then what would be like when you were in your 40s?
Well, in my 40s...
What time is it now?
It's after nine P.M.
Let's talk until it's eleven P.M.
and we make bed.
Well, the mattress.
Get a good night's sleep.
I have one of its mattresses.
Look.
Is that good?
Yes, it is.
Made in China.
Does it sound exotic?
It's definitely made in China.
Have you...
Have you heard about American-made one?
A famous brand in Germany.
The brand.
Does the young man come back?
Yixing has arrived, hasn't he?
Probably.
The one with a suitcase.
You must've had a long trip.
Quick! They're coming back.
Quick.
Shen Teng, Ma Li.
Hello, teachers.
Hello.
Master!
Are you tired?
Have you eaten yet?
Nothing.
I bought you something to eat.
I'm fine. You don't have to.
There's no need.
We have...
I can make you some fried rice.
We made spicy fried chicken,
and you can put it over the rice.
Just like the kind of rice bowl. Want it?
Let Peng decide.
Let's wait for Peng.
Peng will be here soon, right?
Yeah, he's coming soon.
We have something to tell you.
What happened?
Well...
They held an activity
called Shark Loan.
Shark Loan
We lend the house to them
and they trade in with fishing nets.
They gave us all these things.
What should we do?
We sold the rooms upstairs.
Not sold...
Right.
your bedroom is rented.
We mortgaged it.
Now you can't sleep upstairs.
Look they placed a...
Is it black now?
But, this...
I didn't see this coming.
Is it a bit surprised?
He rented this out.
Rent directly from the owner, and move in soon.
Sea-view villa with beautiful terrace.
Well...
Did you discuss it with that guy?
Mr. Huang, Yixing has a question.
No, we didn't discuss it with him.
I'm just asking.
I respect everyone's choice.
Here's the thing.
Your room is worth RMB 2000,
but the room downstairs only worth RMB 300.
Well, if it were you...
RMB 300...
So, here we will
make three very comfortable beds.
I get that first.
[The ad is aired at this period of time]
Honey, you sit there.
No, I want to face
the two teachers.
I just finished watching
Too Cool To Kill
six times!
I invited the whole company to watch.
True.
Yes, I like that movie.
Thanks.
Should we clean this up?
Yeah.
Let's clean it up.
Don't worry. I do.
Does the karaoke machine work?
This one.
Do you want to sing?
We're not doing anything.
And Yixing is here.
Okay.
Why keep him idle?
You want him to sing?
You are so annoying.
The film of yours,
Moon Man,
when is it on?
It should be in summer vacation.
Summer, right?
See,
every time we mention you,
you need to look at the camera.
Find a camera,
and we'll do it again.
The film of yours,
Moon Man,
when is it on?
It should be in summer vacation.
Okay.
Well done.
Thank you.
This is more like it, right?
Did you
force your way in?
I was just leering.
Why is this guy nodding along?
Indeed.
It's not easy to make films.
Yes.
What?
Does it work?
If not, we'll put it back.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Moon Man Concert in Mushroom Cottage.
First, welcome Shen Teng,
who brings you the song "Beijing, Beijing".
Well...
Sis, turn the light switch on and off.
So annoying.
Come back, Sis.
The light.
You're sitting pretty.
You haven't forgotten, have you?
Why are you so troublesome?
No, these two lights don't make the difference.
Right.
Just flash for him.
Whatever
makes him happy.
♪As I walk down every street here♪
No, notice your expressions.
♪I never seem to be at peace♪
Make your hair a little more like him.
Wait a minute. I'll comb my hair back.
♪Except for the roar of engines
and the sound of electricity♪
♪I seemed to hear the throb of his painful heart♪
Shake a little bit more.
♪Here I laugh♪
♪Here I cry♪
You really sound like him.
♪Here I live and here I die♪
He's really dying.
♪Here we pray♪
He can't sing that high.
♪Here we're lost♪
You have the same look in your eyes.
♪Here we seek and here we lose♪
Do you know how to advertise?
♪Shen Teng and Ma Li♪
♪have a movie coming out♪
Stop.
Come back.
♪People are struggling♪
♪standing in line and fighting for tickets♪
♪Yixing and Sis are♪
♪standing in line, dying♪
For the tickets.
♪Walking alone♪
♪Here we laugh♪
Yes. Here I laugh.
♪Here we cry♪
♪Here we live♪
♪and here we die♪
All.
All in this movie.
Right.
♪Moon Man♪
Thank you.
Where is Peng?
Let me ask him.
Ask him where he is.
Don't bother.
There's a boy smiling cheaply at me.
So annoying.
You came home on motorcycle?
Right.
Peng.
[The ad is aired at this period of time]
Come back, Peng.
You've had a long day.
I was on the road for 12 hours.
It's so hard.
Are you hungry?
Do you want to eat?
Do you want to eat something?
Did you eat dinner, bro?
He's been waiting for you.
Take some.
Okay.
Mr. Huang went to heat up the meal again.
This boy.
I'll go.
I'll cook for them. You stay here.
Let me cook. Master.
Let me cook.
Have a rest.
It's fine.
You can talk to them.
Don't worry. I'll cook.
I'll make a quick fried rice.
And a fried chicken with chili.
Almost done.
It looks really good.
But no.
I can't cook
it very well.
Why?
Egg fried rice must be made with overnight rice.
Do you want to try?
You'll take back your words.
But actually,
the egg fried rice
we eat in the streets.
It...
Anyway, the real chef is back.
Teng.
You can have a bowl if you want.
Do you want it?
I'll serve it to the boys first.
Thank you for your hard work.
Teng, help yourself.
It took half a day to get back.
No, I'll serve it to you.
Sis, bring Uncle Shen a small bowl.
He decides to eat again?
No, if you finished...
That's enough.
...then I'll take this.
No.
I'll share a bowl with Uncle Shen.
I can taste some, too.
It smells delicious.
It does look good.
You can use that spoon.
Do you have pickle?
Chicken would be fine, too.
Thanks, Sis.
I'm so sorry, everyone.
I'm late.
I'm so late.
You've had a long day.
No.
Don't be sorry.
Today when you and your brother
were not here,
our family just fell apart.
The five of us
felt really down.
It's like we lost our wits.
Yes.
Without you two,
we can't do anything right
in Live Our Life.
We can't do anything right.
No kidding.
Indeed.
Ask Mr. He.
We felt really sad
when we sat together in the afternoon.
The sun is coming out.
Explain to us.
Thank you.
Really. It's like we lost our wits.
I came here for you two, too.
I didn't expect it took you two this long.
We heard you two weren't there,
and we just wanted to get a plane ticket home.
Yes. We wanted to go then.
When we walked in, there was nobody there.
We just wanted to leave.
He Jiong is my brother,
and he's Ma Li's teacher.
Right.
We're so close, we almost didn't keep them.
We almost didn't keep them
Then they promised them
that you would come back tonight.
It's in the contract.
This is so...
Our family just fell apart.
What a day.
What's this glass for?
It's my presbyopic glasses.
Let me try.
But...
This is stronger than mine.
No, this is too...
Too strong for you?
Because you are nearsighted.
Sorry.
But
I'm comfortable when I look at my phone.
This is for my phone, too.
Not for looking far.
This is presbyopic glasses.
You can't see far by it.
Be quiet, okay?
This is for looking close.
Are you Xu Zheng?
Bro Jiong, you can't see far by it.
Why did you suddenly change into Xu Zheng?
Does Xu Zheng talk like that?
Yes, he talks like that.
Xu Zheng refuses to come.
Xu Zheng and I were in school in the same year.
You two?
Yes.
I also applied for the Beijing Film Academy,
but I didn't get admitted.
Which college?
Beijing Film Academy.
But I think
I shouldn't have been that good, you know?
I ran all over Beijing and China
with my face.
Just with my face.
He was a handsome boy.
Really beautiful.
I may be fat when I grow up,
but my base is there.
Don't put on too much weight, Peng.
Your looks can only get 80 points.
Ours are 90 and 95.
Peng.
Don't eat too much.
I get it.
So annoying.
Did you get beat up as a kid?
When I was a kid, I got beat up every day
because of my beauty.
I want to kick your ass.
What if they cut this into the promo...
The first line would be Shen Teng and Ma Li
visit Mushroom Cottage.
And Mr. Huang's words, "I want to kick your ass."
You brat.
This will be better.
They went straight to blows.
Did we see it right?
Shen Teng kicked Huang Lei.
Huang Lei hit Shen Teng.
Then followed by the sentence of Mr. Huang.
I want to kick your ass.
Right.
You brat.
They went straight to blows.
I don't know what he meant by kicking me.
You...
Why are you eating another bowl?
Just eat.
My brother's had a long day.
And the advertisement and everything.
Let me get you some.
Can't he...
Can't he eat a bite of your rice?
I'll get you some.
Take the chopsticks.
Here, Teng.
I'll get you some.
Teng.
Mr. Huang, it's okay.
I'm an actor after all.
What actor are you?
You know, bro.
I kept laughing.
You know what I'm laughing at?
When the machine plays back,
two hours before
Yixing and Peng came back,
Master wanted
to cook some rice for them,
or cook some dishes.
Mr. Huang said he would
cook some dishes for them.
And Teng said, "Forget it."
"Actors at my age"
"don't eat"
"at this time."
"Let alone them."
Right.
Teng?
Playback.
I don't eat staple food in the evening.
Who as an actor would dare
to eat so much staple food?
Then followed that.
Jiong, when you fill the second bowl,
I see what you mean.
Right?
You don't want to eat.
You're trying to stop these
young people from eating.
One more thing.
My point is
how can I leave what Mr. Huang cooked?
Right.
The audience will misunderstand
that it's not tasty.
Me too.
Right?
I'm gonna pull it out.
But I have to finish this bowl.
Take it.
Cheers.
For the sake of the reputation of Mr. Huang.
[Preview of the Next Episode]
Mr. Huang, we're coming.
Dajing.
Good to see you, Mr. He.
Welcome.
The laborer is here, too.
Pure laborer.
He can trade his strength for money.
He will do anything.
Here, give me the basin.
And pretend that you cut it?
Nice try.
Two.
What a big crab.
Hold it down.
Good job!
Generally,
he should invite us.
Right.
I'm angrier.
Go talk to them.
Director, get here right now!
The pole fell down.
The water is up to my neck.
Boom.
So heavy.
I give up.
Engineering.
Stick to my plan exactly.
Is this part of the plan?
I think I'm going to
eat up everyone's rice.
Shall I bring the rice
cooker to you directly?
He can squat really low.
Why are you clenching your fist?
You two are so childish.
I don't know who really wins,
but you're really crafty.